# Made from http://xmlns.com/foaf/spec/
# elides OnlineChatAccount, OnlineEcommerceAccount, OnlineGamingAccount

PREFIX : <http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/>
PREFIX rdfs: <http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#>
PREFIX wgs84: <http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#>
BASE <http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/>

<Agent> {
  :gender .*;
  :yahooChatID .*;
  :account .*;
  :birthday .*;
  :icqChatID .*;
  :aimChatID .*;
  :jabberID .*;
  :made .*;
  :mbox .*;
  :interest .*;
  :tipjar .*;
  :skypeID .*;
  :topic_interest .*;
  :age .*;
  :mbox_sha1sum .*;
  :status .*;
  :msnChatID .*;
  :openid .*;
  :holdsAccount .*;
  :weblog .*;
} AND (@<Group> OR @<Person> OR @<Organization>)
  # Used with: :maker, :member

<Document> {
  :topic .*;
  :primaryTopic .*;
  :sha1 .*;
} AND (@<Image> OR @<PersonalProfileDocument>)
  AND NOT (@<Project> OR @<Organization>)
  # Used with: rdfs:seeAlso :workInfoHomepage, :workplaceHomepage, :page, :accountServiceHomepage, :openid, :tipjar, :schoolHomepage, :publications, :isPrimaryTopicOf, :interest, :homepage, :weblog

<Group> {
  :member @<Agent>*
}

<Person> {
  :plan .*;
  :surname .*;
  :geekcode .*;
  :pastProject .*;
  :lastName .*;
  :family_name .*;
  :publications @<Document>*;
  :currentProject .*;
  :familyName .*;
  :firstName .*;
  :workInfoHomepage @<Document>*;
  :myersBriggs .*;
  :schoolHomepage @<Document>*;
  :img @<Image>*;
  :workplaceHomepage @<Document>*;
  :knows @<Person>*
} AND @<Agent> AND @wgs84:SpatialThingShape
  AND NOT (@<Project> OR @<Organization>)
# Used with: knows

<OnlineAccount> {
  :accountName .*;
  :accountServiceHomepage @<Document>*
}

wgs84:SpatialThingShape {
  wgs84:lat .;
  wgs84:long .
}

<Organization> {
} AND @<Agent>
  AND NOT (@<Document> OR @<Person>)

<Image> {
  :depicts .*;
  :thumbnail @<Image>*
} AND @<Document>
# Used Wtih img thumbnail depiction

<PersonalProfileDocument> {
} AND @<Document>

<Project> {
} AND NOT (@<Document> OR @<Person>)
